linkbuildingworks.com 2011-04-22

# Privacy Policy LinkBuildingWorks.com, Effective Link Building Services

## Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy does not describe the ways in which Link Building Works may collect or use information obtained through means other than the LinkBuildingWorks.com website. Any questions regarding this Privacy Policy should be directed to [support (at) linkbuildingworks.com](mailto:support@linkbuildingworks.com).

**Collection and Use of Information**   
LinkBuildingWorks.com may collect and store information that you voluntarily supply either while on the LinkBuildingWorks.com website or in responding, via email, to a feature provided on the LinkBuildingWorks.com website. If you decide not to supply or provide LinkBuildingWorks.com with certain information while using the website, LinkBuildingWorks.com may not be able to provide you with some services that are dependent on the collection of this information.

**Information Sharing with Third Parties**  
To make the site more valuable to our visitors, occasionally we may offer some additional features in conjunction with other third party service providers. Accordingly, we may make your information available to these third party service providers. 

LinkBuildingWorks.com will not disclose the information that it collects online from you to allow third parties to use such information to mail or email other promotional offers directly to you unless you have permitted LinkBuildingWorks.com to disclose such information for the purposes of receiving promotional offers from such third parties. If you choose to receive these promotional offers, then your information may be used for direct mail or email marketing. 

In addition, the LinkBuildingWorks.com website includes links to other sites and provides access to products and services offered by third parties, whose privacy policies are separate from this Privacy Policy. When you provide information in the course of obtaining third party products or services through LinkBuildingWorks.com, the use of any information you provide may be governed by the privacy policy of the provider of those third party products or services, even if it appears that you are on Link Building Works-branded pages throughout the transaction. The third party provider's privacy policy may differ from ours and you should contact the third party provider if you have any questions about its privacy practices. Please take special care at all times to be aware of which privacy policy governs your activity on the Internet. 

**Protection of Your Information**   
All information gathered on our site is stored within a LinkBuildingWorks.com-controlled database accessible only to LinkBuildingWorks.com. However, as effective as any security measure may be, no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our database, nor can we guarantee that information you supply won't be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
We are continually making changes and improvements to the services we offer through LinkBuildingWorks.com. If we need to change our Privacy Policy at some point in the future, we will post the changes before they take effect. If you have any questions about the LinkBuildingWorks.com Privacy Policy, please contact [support (at) linkbuildingworks.com](mailto:support@linkbuildingworks.com).

### Latest from blog

Every search engine continuously upgrades itself to deliver more relevant results to its users. As the process of indexing plays a major role with regard to what appears on SERPs, search engines adopt
